So how long have you been in America?
- A year and a half.
- No kidding.
(Leonard:)- You speak English really well.
- So do you.
(Dennis:)Except for your tendency
to end sentences with prepositions.
(Leonard:)What are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)That.
(Sheldon:)He's not wrong.
All right, and this is my office.
- Is this part of the tour?
- Nope. Goodbye.
(Sheldon:)Sheldon,
we've hardly shown him anything.
All right, this is my desk.
These are my books.
(Sheldon:)This is my door.
Please close it behind you, goodbye.
(Dennis:)You're doing work
in quantum loop corrections.
- Keen observation, goodbye.
- You see where you went wrong, don't you?
(Sheldon:)- Leonard.
- Ha.
(Leonard:)- Yeah?
- Get him out.
Come, I'll show you the rec center.
They've got Nautilus equipment.
Do I look like I lift weights?